太棒了
This is awesome.
我真不敢相信 这个时刻终于到来了
I can't believe this moment's finally here.
再开一英里 我的爱车就 开了200,000英里了
One more mile and my little boy turns 200,000.
你的宝贝菲奥罗 已经开成老爷车了
Your baby Fiero's grown into a really old man Fiero.
一个糟老头
And just like an old man,
爱流口水 闻起来臭烘烘
he leaks fluid, smells stale,
走路的时候还放屁
makes weird noises out the back.
确实是
Yeah, he does.
把雪茄从车柜里拿出来
Hey, light up those cigars in the glove compartment.
这是地道的古巴雪茄 去年在唐人街买的
They're real Cubans. I got 'em in Chinatown last year
就是为了这个时刻
just for this moment.
我不想说说你被宰了
Uh, Marshall, I'm not saying you were definitely ripped off,
但他们确实是包在纸巾中的筷子
but these are chopsticks wrapped in napkins.
- 你说什么? - 注意 下水道盖
- What are you talking about? - Whoa, pothole.
什么? 别 别
What? No. Oh. No.
别这样啊
No, no, no.
只有0.8英里就到了 加油啊 哥们
No, there's only .8 miles to go. Come on, buddy.
兄弟
Buddy!
我点燃他们还有意义?
Is it cool if I still light these?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史
第二季 第十七集
翻译：    唐伯虎点雷管   校对：     Alice
后期：     oliver0951      字幕监制：  叶煦
孩子们 生活有时候 强迫我们做不愿做的事
Kids, sometimes life forces us to be someone we didn't want to be.
这种事情发生时 我们总要试着保留点自我
When that happens, we often try to hold on to a little piece of who we were.
比方说一个纹身
Maybe a tattoo.
或者一个小首饰
Or a piece of jewelry.
一个微不足道的纪念品提醒我们 "这才是真的自我"
A tiny souvenir that reminds us, "This is who I really am."
马修的纪念品可不小
Marshall's souvenir was not so tiny,
他从现实世界得到的越多
but the more he found himself being pushed toward the corporate world
离他的保护环境的理想就越远
and away from his dream of saving the environment,
他对菲奥罗就看的越重
the tighter he held on to that Fiero.
Hey.
我们今天肯定赶不上叠纸聚会了
One good thing: we're off the hook for the folding party today.
这对我和莉莉来说很重要的
Hey. It's very important to both Lily and me
我们俩都要 为我们婚礼做个折纸鸟...
that there be a handmade origami crane in each of our wedding's...
其实我根本不会折 谢天谢地
I couldn't even get through it. Thank God.
你的车会修好的
Hey, your car's going to be fine.
这是附近最好的修车行了
This is the best auto shop around.
看这个证书
Look at this certificate.
这其中一个技师
One of the mechanics here
吃光了64盎司牛排
finished a 64-ounce steak.
惊喜吧
Surprise.
我们觉得你们俩不来没意思
We felt bad that you guys were missing
超有趣的手工叠纸聚会 所以...
the super-fun origami folding party, so...
我们建议到这来
we suggested moving it here.
我们坚持这样 (没有征求他意见)
We insisted.
好极了
Terrific.
菲奥雷怎么样了
How's the Fiero?
她还在治疗呢
She's still in triage.
她?我还以为是你当他是男的
She? I thought it was your little boy.
它可男可女 他是辆会变性的车
Oh, it goes back and forth. It's sort of a tranny car.
你开她多久了 应该是他
How long have you had her... slash him?
我16岁时我哥留给我了
My brothers handed it down to me when I was 16.
他们太好了
Oh, how nice of them.
也不算
Not really.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
菲奥雷是你的了
The Fiero is yours.
如果你通过最后的考试
If you pass the final test.
快啊
Come on!
我在房间里已经刮光腿毛 还把5美元分四份吞了下去
I already shaved my legs and swallowed five dollars in quarters.
只拉出来4.5美元
Only $4.50 has come out.
那去威纳汉堡汽车外卖
Just go to the Weinerburger drive-thru
帮我们买12杯咖啡
and get us 12 cups of coffee.
- 就这个? - 恩 就这个
- That's it? - Oh, yeah.
但我们决定你穿什么
But we get to decide what you wear.
同意 完全同意
Agreed. Totally agreed.
你裸体啊
You're naked.
我知道
I'm aware of that.
有50美分吗
You have 50 cents?
没有
No...
我只想要咖啡 行吗?
Look, can I just have my coffee, please?
对不起 我们没有托架和盖了
Sorry, we're all out of trays and lids.
两个高个的家伙几分钟前 过来把他们都买了
Two tall guys just came through here a few minutes ago and bought 'em all.
这就是马修愚蠢的
And that is the origin of Marshall's insane
"禁止车内有食物 饮料 甚至杂货" 规定的出处
"no food or drinks in the Fiero, not even groceries" rule.
这不愚蠢
It is not insane.
\这好像是你连续叠坏的第三个
Barney. That's like the third one in a row that you've screwed up.
我正在试 但它...
Well, I'm trying, but it's...
听着 演中线对折两次 把尾巴拉出来
Look. You fold twice to the middle, fold back and forth, pull the ends out,
翻过来 打开 再折边 折头 再对折
flip over, open the flaps, fold the edges, crease the front, fold in half,
把翅膀向下拉 推到底角 在把翅膀拉出来
fold the wings down, push in the bottom corners, and fold the wings back out.
你难道想让小孩给你示范?
Or would you like one of my kindergartners to show you?
等等 我想我知道怎么弄了
Wait, wait, wait. Wait, I think I've got it.
不
No.
算了吧 纸太贵了 你别弄了
Forget it; the paper's too expensive. You're out.
胡扯
Aw, nerts.
食物规定是愚蠢的 我们差点因为这个死了
The food rule is insane. We could have died because of it.
- 还记得100,000英里时的惨痛经历 - 费奥罗的惨败(fiero-asco拆字)
- Remember the 100K fiasco? - Ah, the Fiero-asco.
兄弟 我告诉你不行 它已经跑了100,000英里了
Dude, I told you that doesn't work. It's the 100K fiasco.
- 什么是100,000英里时的惨痛经历 - 是费奥罗的惨痛经历?
- What's the 100K fiasco? - The Fiero-asco?
那是在大学第一年寒假之前
It was just before winter break our freshman year of college.
马修和我是室友 但我们那时还不是好朋友
Marshall and I were roommates, but we weren't really good friends yet.
我觉得泰德有点自命不凡
I thought Ted was a little bit pretentious.
马修是个大懒汉
And Marshall was a total slob.
Hey.
假期结束的话 我开着我的菲奥雷来学校
I'm driving my Fiero back over break.
我知道虽然我们互相都看腻了
I know we see enough of each other as it is,
但你想搭车的话 我可以多花点油钱
but if you want a ride, I could use the gas money.
你住俄亥俄州 不是吗? 我可以绕点道去接你
You live in Ohio, right? I could swing through and pick you up.
打住 首先 我父母住俄亥俄州
All right, first of all, my parents live in Ohio.
我现在住这(我活在当下,Ted又在帅酷)
I live in the moment.
凯伦和我从感恩节就再也没见了
Plus, Karen and I haven't seen each other since Thanksgiving.
我们都想弥补这么 远距离的相思...
We're both really invested in making this long-distance thing work, so...
改主意的话给我打电话
All right, well, call me if you change your mind.
我的车要冲击100K英里了
My odometer's going to hit 100K.
如果我提前走的话 凯伦会很无聊的
She'd be so bummed if I left early.
都出了问题
It was totally mutual.
我意思是 凯伦挑起的 但我...
I mean, Karen brought it up first, but I...
但是 双方都有错
it was... it was totally mutual.
我听见了
I hear you.
那你和莉莉怎么样?是认真的吗?
So what's up with you and Lily? Anything serious?
那当然
Yeah.
兄弟 我们大学才刚开始
Dude, we're college freshmen.
我怎么会为了 一颗树而放弃整座森林
I'm not going to get tied down by the first chick I hook up with.
莉莉很好 但是我 不会和她认真的 你知道吗?
Lily's cool, but this bird you'll never chain, you know?
接下来的几个小时车程是经典公路旅行
The next few hours of our drive were classic road trip.
这首歌...
So... this song.
这是世界上最好听的歌了
Oh, it's the best song in the world.
我唯一喜欢的歌
It's the only song I like.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
磁带卡在录音机里面了 好像两年了
Tape's been stuck in the player for, like, two years.
反正比什么没有强
Better than nothing, though.
也许吧
Maybe.
我真的对这首歌感到恶心了
I am so... sick... of this song.
别担心 又要重放了
Don't worry. It comes around again.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
# Just to be the man who walks 1,000 miles #
# And falls down at your door... #
我们终于从头唱到尾了
Yeah, we totally nailed the ending.
这可能是我们唱的最好的一次了
That was probably our best one.
你玩过Zitch dog的游戏吗?
Hey, you want to play Zitch Dog?
- 什么? - 是个在车上玩得游戏
- What? - Uh, it's a car game.
每见到一次狗 你就得马上说 "Zitch dog"
Every time you see a dog, you got to be the first one to say, "Zitch dog."
- 我玩得很好 所以... - Zitch dog
- I'm pretty good, so... - Zitch dog.
不 我不知道我们已经... 我们开始 但是
Well, no, I didn't know we had... we'd started, but...
行吧 你得第一分
Okay, that's cool. You got the first point.
- Zitch dog - 该死
- Zitch dog. - Zitch dog. Damn it!
我们还要玩?  因为 我不是 我不是真的...
Are we still playing? 'Cause I wasn't... I wasn't really...
12比0
12-nothing.
马修
Marshall.
- 马修 - Zitch dog  blue Suburban  (狗品种)
- Marshall. - Zitch dog, blue Suburban.
该死
Damn it!
18比0
18-nothing.
然后马修忙于 在Zitch dog游戏中耍赖
Then Marshall, who was so busy cheating at Zitch Dog,
让我们迷路了
got us totally lost.
我们他妈的在哪?
Where the hell are we?!
等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
我想你跳过了一些东西
I think you skipped something.
真的吗? 听起来不可能
Really? Seems impossible.
我们还有点时间
Hey, we got some time.
你说我们下高速 去以前没怎么开过的路 怎么样?
What do you say we get off the highway, take the road less traveled, you know?
Robert Frost.
这主意不太好
Doesn't seem like a smart idea.
时间太迟了
Too late.
我从这个出口下
I'm taking this exit.
是谁不够幽默呢 凯伦?
Who's not fun enough now, Karen?
然后我们迷路了
Then we got lost.
我们他妈的在哪?
Where the hell are we?!
- 我靠边吧 - 别 继续开
- I'm pulling over. - No, keep driving.
我们已经快没油了 而且我们可能都不在马路上了
We're almost out of gas, and we might not even be on a road anymore.
外面零下了 我们要是靠边 我们会被雪困上几天了
It's below zero out. If we pull over, we could be snowed in for days.
我只有 6个格兰诺拉条和三瓶水
Plus, I only have, like, six granola bars and three bottles of water.
- 我早丢出去了 - 什么?
- Nah, I threw them out. - What?!
菲奥雷上严禁食物和饮料
No food or drink in the Fiero.
严禁食物和水? 你多久开始就没洗床单了
No food or drink in the F...? You haven't washed your sheets since...
这样开始了 我们生命最长的夜晚
Thus began the longest night of our lives.
我脚肯定冻僵了
Pretty sure that my foot is frozen solid.
马修...
Marshall...
这下很有可能我们被雪困上几天了
there's a very real chance that we're gonna be snowed in here for days.
如果我先死了 为了活下去你可以随便把我怎么样
If I die first, do whatever you need to survive.
吃我的肉
Eat my flesh.
把我象星球大战巨兽剖开 随便怎样...
Slice me open like a tauntaun, whatever.
谢了 泰德
Thanks, Ted.
你是个好友
You're a good friend.
如果我死了 你不能动我的尸体
And if I die first, you just leave my body alone.
什么?
What?
我刚刚还说了你可以剖开我 钻到我身体里
I just said you could cut me open and crawl inside me.
别跟我说这些 太恶心了
Yeah, don't do any of that stuff to me; it skeeves me out.
但... 要是你死了 如果我不...也的死啊
But... but you're dead, and I'm gonna die if I don't.
很难决定啊
Wasn't an easy decision.
都是你那愚蠢的 不能放食物的规定
This is all because of your insane no-food rule.
这绝对是理性的决定
It's perfectly rational.
我的眼镜
Hey! My spectacles!
Hey.
我知道我们快没油了
I know we're low on gas,
但我们能开会暖气?
but can we turn on the heat for just a minute?
Okay.
兄弟
Dude...
我不想这么说
I hate to say this...
但是真的好冷
but it's so cold...
只有一个办法我们能渡过今晚了
there's only one way that we're gonna make it through this night.
- 我们应该继续向前开 - 别这样 马修
- We should've kept driving. - Come on, Marshall.
我们说不定现在已经挂了
No. No. We might die now.
我再也见不到莉莉了
I may never see Lily again.
我没有告诉过任何人这事 但是...
I never told anybody this, but...
我早知道了我会和这个女孩结婚
I've known for a long time that I'm gonna marry that girl.
如果我们活下来了 我有一天一定娶她
If we survive this, someday I'm gonna marry her.
对于你的眼镜 我很抱歉
I'm sorry about your spectacles.
没事
That's okay.
它们是装饰用的
They were decorative.
马修
Hey, Marshall.
怎么了
Yeah?
你还在想莉莉?
Are you still thinking about Lily?
Yeah.
请别想了
Please stop.
接下来马修和我都以为 我们会死在这偏僻的地方
And so Marshall and I thought we were gonna die out there in the middle of nowhere.
但是有趣的事发生了...
But funny thing...
你们这对恋人 最好不要停在这
Hey. You lovers better just keep on driving.
- Zitch dog! - 该死
- Zitch dog! - Damn it!
你那么久之前就说了要娶我啊?
You said you were gonna marry me that long ago?
太感动了
That is so sweet.
这趟旅行让我俩成为了好朋友
That trip is when Marshall and I became best friends.
听起来好像就你有特权
With privileges, from the sound of it.
埃里克森
Eriksen.
Wow.
他现在需要个拥抱
Looks like he really needs a hug.
泰德
Ted.
他说让它能再开动 至少花3,000美元
He said it would be at least 3,000 bucks to make it run again.
就是这样 还不敢打保票
And even then, there's no guarantee.
算了 它确实是太旧了
Well, it's a pretty old car.
你可以继续延长它寿命
Yeah. You can keep prolonging its life,
但毕竟 它只是一个机器
but it's really mostly machine at this point.
我知道要花很多钱
I know that it's a lot of money,
但是它是我的菲奥雷 你知道吗?
but it's my Fiero, you know?
我就要毕业了 还可以靠当法人律师赚点外快
I'm about to graduate and take some sellout corporate law job,
没有了它 我就像跟那个穿西装 行尸走肉一样了
and without that Fiero, I'm just another guy in a suit.
你疯了啊 干嘛扯到我
- How dare you... - Hey.
这辆车和我一起经历了太多太多
I've been through so much in that car.
自杀的猫
The suicidal cat.
搭车的沃尔特
Hitchhiking Waldo.
打烂车窗的流浪汉
The homeless guy who broke in through the window
还在杂物都撇在后座
and threw up all over the backseat.
莉莉 别...
Lily, don't.
坚强点 别让我陷入囚徒困境 (两头为难)
Be strong. Do not go all "prisoner's dilemma" on me.
这车就要报废了 罗宾 我得有良心啊
The car's on its deathbed, Robin. I have to clear my conscience.
你们说什么呢?
Guys, what are you talking about?
我们遇到罗宾没多久
Okay. Shortly after we met Robin,
她和我都对同个地方的 泰国菜上瘾了
she and I were jonesing for Thai food from this one place.
外卖得等一个半小时 我们等不及了
An hour and a half delivery. We can't wait that long.
我希望我们能用菲奥雷 但马修有个愚蠢的不能放食物的规定
I wish we could take the Fiero, but Marshall has this insane no-food rule.
但是是泰国菜啊 莉莉
But Thai food, Lily.
Pad Yum Mao (菜名)
Pad Yum Mao.
Tom Kai Gah (菜名)
Tom Kai Gah.
Thai See Ran (菜名)
Thai See Ran.
连你随便报的几个菜名 也听起来这么好吃
Oh! You're just saying random syllables, and it still sounds delicious.
好的 我们开车去吧
Okay. Here's what we'll do.
我们开过去 拿了菜 把它们包两层
We'll drive over, pick it up, have them double-bag it,
把窗户打开非常小心的开回来
very carefully drive it back here with the windows open,
他肯定不知道的
and he'll never know.
这刹车也太灵了...
Wow, these brakes are really sensitive.
马修会杀了我的
Oh, Marshall is gonna kill me!
这件事和 关于"affect"和"effect"的区别那件事
This and the difference between "affect" and "effect" are the only two things
他真的对这两个较真的
he's really serious about.
- 莉莉 会没事的 - 不 出事了
- Lily, it's gonna be fine. - No, it's not.
天啊 马修会发飙的 我们怎么办啊
Marshall's gonna freak. Oh, God, oh, God. What are we gonna do?
-咋办啊 -闭嘴
- Oh, God, oh...! - Shut up!
现在听我的 时间在流逝
Now, listen to me. The clock is ticking.
首先 我们把所有 豆腐和菜叶子拣起来
Okay, first thing, we scoop up all these little pieces of tofu and cabbage.
然后 我们需要做的 就是清理乱七八糟的东西
Next, what we need to take care of are the really messy parts--
还有汤 我们要把它弄干
the pools that have collected. We got to soak that soup up.
最后是我们需要 把Tom Kah Gai的味盖住
Last is the smell. We got to cover up that Tom Kah Gai.
你说有雪茄
You mentioned cigars.
两个在车柜里面 他一直留着的
There's two in the glove compartment, but he's been saving them.
把那些筷子递给我
Hand me those chopsticks.
来点音乐吧?
Hey, how about some tunes?
太好听了
Oh, great song.
这些雪茄根本没有用啊
These cigars aren't helping at all.
确实不是个好主意
Yeah. This was a terrible idea.
闻起来就像流浪汉躺过一样
Now it just smells like a homeless guy threw up in here.
砸坏的玻璃?
The broken windows?
我们想看起来更真实
We had to make it look realistic.
那你砸坏两个干嘛
Why did you break two of them?
看她砸窗挺好玩的 我也试了一次
It looked like fun when she did it. So I wanted to try.
真不敢相信是你们俩干的
Can't believe this whole time it was you guys.
我还一直怪那个穿紧身衣 深色皮肤的舞蹈演员
I've been blaming really tanned dancing leotard guy.
马修 对不起 但这个秘密也
Marshall, I'm so sorry, but sharing that secret--
让罗宾和我成为最好的朋友了
that's when Robin and I became best friends.
太特殊的车了
Wow. What a special car.
现在还要报废吗
So, can I crush it into a little cube yet?
我不知道
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
快点 马修
Come on, Marshall.
这是你的
This is your Fiero.
你知道该怎么做
You know the right thing to do here.
你为什么这么爱这车?
Wow, Barney, why do you love that car so much?
爱它?
Love it?
等会
Hold on a second.
爱它?
Love it?
我恨他
I hate it!
怎么了?为什么?
What? Why?
为什么?为什么?
Why? Why?
为什么?!
Why?!
- 为什么?! - 我来告诉你们!
- Why?! - Let me tell it.
去年交通系统罢工的时候
It was last year during the transit strike.
- Hey. - Hey.
马修在吗?
Uh, is Marshall around?
我半个小时后要去皇后区按摩 我需要他送我一程
I have a massage in Queens in half an hour. I need a ride.
他一整天都在图书馆 钥匙在那...
Uh, no, he's at the library all day. Just take the keys.
你为什么不开车送送我呢
Hey! Why don't you drive me?
你也可以顺便兜兜风
It'll be like a total road trip.
到皇后区兜风?
To Queens?
我们可以买点牛肉干 饼干
Yeah, we'll get, we'll get beef jerky, Triscuits.
但我还有好多事情做
Uh, actually I have a lot of work to do, so.
那好吧 我去取消按摩
Okay. Well, anyway, I'll cancel.
- 再见 - 等等
- See you later. - Wait!
你知道怎么开车吧 不是吗？
You know how to drive, right?
当然知道了 我热爱驾驶
What, of course I know how to drive. I love driving.
在公路上飞驰
Hitting the road.
在小路上漫游
Cruising the lanes.
还有刹车
And braking.
鸣笛 爱死了
Honking. Love it.
除了女驾驶员
Except for lady drivers.
别让我碰到女驾驶员
Don't get me started on lady drivers.
- 那个踏板是油门? - 你想骗我？
- Which pedal's the gas? - Trick question.
- 不是 - 是
- No, it's not. - Yes, it is.
- 不是 - 中间 左边 还是右边
- No, it's not. - Middle, left, right?
我没学过怎么开车
I never learned how to drive!
我在城市里长大的 没机会
I grew up in the city. I never had a chance.
你知道吗
Well, guess what?
你有机会学了 因为我来教你
You're getting your chance. Because I'm going to teach you.
巴尼・斯蒂森 系安全带
Barney Stinson, buckle up.
别这样了
This isn't right.
老天决不会允许我们 用这么快的速度来开车的
God never meant for us to travel at such breakneck speeds.
放松点 你做得挺好的
Relax. You're doing great.
别看那的那个老太太 这不是比赛
Ignore the old lady on the rascal; this isn't a race.
兄弟 一条狗
Dude, a dog.
Zitch dogs...他不懂
Zitch dogs, this. Or nothing.
我应该怎么办?告诉我干嘛 泰德
What do I do? Tell me what to do, Ted.
踩刹车 二十分钟内踩都来得及
Step on the brakes. Sometime in the next 20 minutes.
哪个啊? 哪个是刹车?
Which? Which one's the break again?
- 左边那个 - 左边 左边
- The left one. - Left. Oh, man, left.
- 我大脑一片空白 - 手成L型
- I'm totally blanking. - Make the Ls.
我们停不下来了啊
Oh, we're not going to make it.
为什么打开收音机啊?
Why did you just turn on the radio?
我也不知道为什么打开啊
I don't know why I turned on the radio!
我们要死了 告诉我怎么办 泰德
We're going to die. Tell me what to do, Ted.
放松点 你太紧张了
Relax. You're being crazy.
- 帮帮我 泰德! 我说真的 - 刹车 换档 转向
- Help me, Ted! I'm being serious. - Stop, drop and roll.
尖叫真爽! 尖叫真爽!
Screaming is fun! Screaming is fun!
我不能动了
I can't move.
我不能 我失去...知觉
I can't... I can't feel my...
等等
Wait.
我们没事
We're okay.
- 我们没事 - 我们没事
- We're okay. - We're okay.
真是个奇迹 泰德!
It's a miracle, Ted!
看起来你在车里发生不止一次事故了
Wow. Sounds like you had some accident in that car.
确切说 他有两次事故如果加上他...
Actually, he had two accidents if you add the fact that he...
ummina-hummina-hummina-hummina ummina-hummina-hummina-hummina.
我都不可能 在这如果不是那次事故
I shouldn't even be here, thanks to that deathtrap.
但是天意...
But fate...
天意给了我第二次机会
fate gave me a second chance.
让我意识到我们 在世上的时间太少了 不能浪费
And helped me realize that our days on this planet are too few to squander.
所以我决定从现在开始
So I decided from that moment on
尽情的继续生活
to continue living life to its fullest.
我作了一个终生不变的决定 就是绝不改变生活方式
So you made a life-changing decision to not change your life at all.
是这样的
True story.
朋友们
Guys.
这辆菲奥雷对我们意味着太多
This Fiero's meant a lot to all of us.
友谊的建立
Friendships were made.
冒险的经历 可怕的事故
Adventures had. Horrors faced.
就是我们要解脱它的原因
That's why we have to get rid of it.
- 是的! - 什么?
- Yes! - What?
它有着精彩的过去 现在它需要的是骄傲的死去
It's lived a great life and it deserves to die with dignity.
但是200,000英里
But 200,000...
这就是生活 你知道吗?
But that's life. You know?
你不知道你将会怎么样
You never end up where you thought you wanted to be.
我不是瞎起哄
I'm not helping the environment.
泰德没有成为哲学家
Ted's not a philosopher.
莉莉没有成为享誉世界的艺术家
Lily's not not a world-famous artist.
巴尼开一个小时车也没到10英里
Barney's never driven more than ten miles an hour.
罗宾 我肯定 她的生活也有沮丧的经历
Robin, I'm sure, has also experienced disappointment in her life.
也许?
Maybe?
我的菲奥雷 不是一个简单的 开了200,000英里的菲奥雷
And my Fiero's not a Fiero that went 200,000 miles.
没什么 你们知道吗?
It's okay. You know?
它们都是过去的梦想了
Those are old dreams.
我们买个新车 开始新的生活
We'll get a new car and we'll fill that one up with new memories.
我们结婚的时候会是这辆车
And that'll be the car we had when we were first married.
当我们有了自己的房子 是这辆车
When we owned our first house.
甚至当我们有四个孩子了 还是这辆车
Maybe even the first car our four kids remember.
太好了
That's so sweet.
但最好我们是头两个孩子记住的车
The first car our two kids remember.
我想说再见了
I would like to say good-bye.
你知道吗?
You know what?
这辆菲奥雷 影响了我们的生活
This Fiero, it's effected all our lives.
- 是影响(发音不一样) - 我是说影响
- Affected. - That's what I said.
只是确认一下
Just making sure.
这辆车带我们去了很多地方
Got us all a lot of places.
我想现在是我们该帮帮它的时候了
I mean maybe it's time we return the favor.
我们应该让它跑到200,000英里
This Fiero should have made it to 200,000.
让我们把它推出去
So, let's get it out that door.
我们推完最后.7英里
And we'll push it the last .7 miles.
对我们也意义非凡
It'd do the same for us.
嘿 天才们
Hey, geniuses.
后轮锁上了 车根本动不了
The back wheels are on blocks. That car ain't going anywhere.
- 到此为止! - 到此为止!
- Close enough! - Close enough!
就这样马修 跟他的菲奥雷说再见了
And so Marshall said good-bye to his Fiero.
而那辆车还给了我们最后的礼物
And as the car's final gift to us all,
我们在接下来的两天 在酒吧消费零部件所卖的钱
the money he got for scrap parts paid our bar tab for the next two nights.
再会  菲奥雷! (意大利语)
Arrivederci, Fiero!
你给了车中的无私奉献者
You were the freaking giving tree of cars.
祝你安静的离开
May you rust in peace.
下地狱吧 魔鬼
Rot in hell, devil steed.
还有比那样更好的朋友吗?
And what better friend is there than that?
兄弟 听过这首歌吗?
Bro. Have you heard this new song?
我刚拿到的卡带
I just got the cassingle.
放进去吧
Put it in.
我永远不会厌倦这首歌
I am never going to get sick of this song.
绝不 绝不
Never, ever, never, never, ever.
Yeah!